newsoftwares.net 2012-07-28

# Privacy Policy - New Softwares.net Security Products | Online Backup Solutions

Privacy Policy

At New Softwares.net, our most important asset is our relationship with you.

New Softwares.net is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users. This Privacy & Security Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website www.New Softwares.net (the "Site") and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the "Service"). "Personal information" for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your name, address, phone number, fax number or email address.

New Softwares.net stresses its privacy and security standards to guard against identity theft and provide security for your personal information. We regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges.

GlobalSign

New Softwares.net is certified through the GlobalSign Web Privacy Seal Program. GlobalSign is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. In order to obtain certification, New Softwares.net disclosed its information privacy practices to GlobalSign for its review to ensure compliance with GlobalSign's requirements. If you contact us with a privacy-related concern as directed in this Policy and do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or if your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should contact GlobalSign. GlobalSign will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

Your use of the Services is voluntary. You may stop using and uninstall any New Softwares.net software at any time. By downloading the New Softwares.net software and/or using the Service, You acknowledge and agree that certain New Softwares.net software and/or plug-ins may collect and use non-personally identifiable information relating to your use of the Service (such as IP address, browser type, referring URL). 

New Softwares.net is committed to providing a high-performance, secure, easy-to-use online backup service. Data collected is used exclusively with the goal of providing and improving this service.

No Spam

New Softwares.net will not sell, rent, trade or give away your email address or other contact information to any other organization.

No Spyware/Adware/Malware

New Softwares.net software is designed to backup your files online and contains no spyware or other unwanted applications.

No Third Party Advertising

New Softwares.net does not intend to advertise for other organizations through its website or email communications.

Your Data is Protected

New Softwares.net encrypts all data on your system and then sends it to New Softwares.net over an encrypted connection to ensure your data is secure.

We aim to provide you an excellent experience with our service. For additional detail on how we handle your data or to contact us with questions, please see the rest of the Privacy Policy below.

Information Collection

Website Cookies and Logs

When you visit [www.New Softwares.net](http://www.newsoftwares.net/) and other [New Softwares.net](http://www.newsoftwares.net/) websites, our servers automatically collect certain information such as your IP address, browser type, page requested, cookies, etc. This information is used to provide a custom experience, keep your session active, or improve the service.

Information You Provide

You may provide information such as your name, email address, or other requested information to purchase or use the service. You may also provide us information when you email or call us, or through feedback and other forms on the website.

Backup Service

By using the online backup service, the system automatically encrypts and transfers your files to secure cloud where data sits in encrypted form. Only certain information will be available to[ New Softwares.net](http://www.newsoftwares.net/) such as type of operating system, file types, or sizes to enable New Softwares.net to provide the service or help support you. 

New Softwares.net will never look at your actual files. New Softwares.net does not intentionally gather information about visitors under the age of 13.

Sharing and Disclosures

New Softwares.net does not disclose personal information to service providers, except to process credit card transactions. The data used to process credit card transactions adheres to a strict privacy policy supported by GlobalSign, VeriSign and McAfee PCI Compliance. 

New Softwares.net may use third party service providers (e.g. hosting providers) and your data will only be stored in encrypted form and only as necessary to provide you the service. We may share certain aggregated non-personal information (such as total volume of data New Softwares.net stores) with third parties.

Law Enforcement

New Softwares.net may disclose personal data to third parties, with or without notice, (a) where required by law, (b) to protect and defend the rights of New Softwares.net, (c) or to enforce the New Softwares.net Terms of Service.

Corporate Change

If New Softwares.net is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Security

New Softwares.net is committed to the security of your data and has put in place industry standard physical and electronic enforcement mechanisms. New Softwares.net products automatically encrypt your data before transmission and send the encrypted data using industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. Your data is stored in a secure location with access controls for authorized employees only.

Communication

From time to time, New Softwares.net will communicate with you via email to inform you of service-related information such as confirmation of a password change, expiration of a credit card, notification of a service issue, or availability of a new product or feature from New Softwares.net We will not contact you excessively or to promote other third party products. In addition to email, we may contact you via phone for, support reasons only, if you provide us your phone number.

Updating or Removing Information

Users may update or remove their information by signing in to [www.newsoftwares.net ](http://www.newsoftwares.net/) or contacting New Softwares.net Support to remove your information, please visit your account and click "Cancel Account." If you cancel your account, some of your data may still be retained in our archives or backups.

Privacy Policy Changes

New Softwares.net may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We expect these changes to be minor. New policies will be posted to [www.newsoftwares.net/privacy](http://www.newsoftwares.net/privacy) and, for material changes, we will announce more prominently (including potential email notification.) Your continued usage of the Service expressly constitutes consent.

Safe Harbor

New Softwares.net supports the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles as covered in this Privacy Policy.

Privacy Complaints

New Softwares.net is committed to protecting your privacy. If you have a privacy complaint, please contact us directly first to attempt to resolve any issue by visiting our [Privacy-Policy](http://www.newsoftwares.net/privacy).

Contacting New Softwares.net

To view the latest version of this Privacy Policy and for any questions, comments, suggestions, or concerns, please contact us.
